Good morning.
I think it's time for a good morning.
Noon.
Good afternoon.
Studio.
Good morning, sir.
The old year's this way.
But there's a table right here.
This way?
Yeah, I think it's that way.
Let's just have dinner and leave if there's any inconvenience.
Yes, sir.
This will be a surprise rehearsal.
We'll do it just as we did at the beginning.
We're going over a few details right now.
We'll get to it as soon as we're done.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you for watching!
I knew it!
car
me
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching Thank you for watching!
I won't interrupt.
Just no.
Is everything okay?
I hope you're okay.
Good night.
The way your legs look so nervous.
Night child
please?
Yoriko
Thank you for watching.
Day 1 is over. The star of the show, Yoriko, is not here.
I'm sorry, please be patient with the waitress.
It's over!
Day 1 was the first day because Yuzu was night and day.
First shot on the first day
Good work Good work Good work
Cheer up, everyone!
I was waiting for you, Yoruko
I saw you. I really saw you.
Nervous?
No, but...
I think I managed to hold it together. I wonder if I managed to force myself to break down.
I managed on the 1st day.
Good job, good job Minami!
Yuzu's excitement was great!
We made it through!
That was it, wasn't it?
That story
After that, we were all clammy.
Oh, yeah?
You know, on the radio.
I said something like, "This song...
I read it on the radio.
I was like, "What? You don't like anything?
That was great, Waitress. You're a great player.
They were great players, really... and they stayed on stage and watched us afterwards.
I'll see you tomorrow. Tomorrow?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Let's do our best. Let's do our best.
Let's do our best.
Yes, it's the second day of the Idols stage.
Oh, it's finally the second day!
Yes, I know, there are only two more performances left...
I'll do my best for the next two performances!
Your makeup was sparkling today.
Yes, I changed my makeup a little bit today.
Well, I had the top one battened down and the bottom one glittery. Um, I had the top made into a bat and only the bottom made sparkly!
I changed my hair a little bit.
I changed it a little bit.
But I still have the piyo-piyo...
I think she's still there.
But please wait for me!
Let's do our best!
Are you twirling?
Today is the 26th
Yuzu, it's your first day, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's your first shot.
She suddenly sat down next to me.
Oh, no.
I'm so nervous.
I did it yesterday.
You were practicing earlier in rehearsal.
I could hear you getting excited.
But I'm really embarrassed.
You're embarrassed? You don't look embarrassed.
I said some things.
When we're running, you're gonna open the door.
You did it yesterday.
Hey.
Hey!
It's yuzu! It's Yuzu!
We were laughing so much at that time.
We were all laughing.
Because we laughed when he said, "Do it!
That's right.
He was praising her so much.
Because you were so good at enlivening the audience.
The place was so warm.
- I'm so happy! - I'll go ahead now.
I'll go ahead now.
Let's go to that place.
I'm off!
Day 2, Misaki came to see us!
I was so moved. I really was.
Thanks a lot!
Seino's Gurgle channel!
GO!
I'll watch it at night too.
We haven't filmed this opening in forever.
Yeah, we haven't filmed it.
That's right.
We'll use this for the opening.
The back?
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
That's great. It's great.
I don't want to come back to the memory I took yesterday?
I didn't. Iyoko came yesterday.
I hope you enjoy the performance part!